<resources>
    <string name='app_name'>MediAlert</string>
    <string name='slogan'>Your Personal Medication Assistant</string>
    <string name='email'>Email</string>
    <string name='click_to_register'>click to register</string>
    <string name='registration'>Registration</string>
    <string name='click_to_login'>Click here to login</string>

    <string name="health_article_content">
    <![CDATA[
        <b><font color="#004281">BMI Categories:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#004281">------------------------</font><br/><br/>

        <font color="#004281">->Underweight = less than 18.5 </font><br/>
        <font color="#004281">->Normal weight = 18.5–24.9  </font><br/>
        <font color="#004281">->Overweight = 25–29.9     </font><br/>
        <font color="#004281">->Obesity = BMI of 30 or greater</font><br/><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Recommendations based on BMI categories:</font><br/> <font color="#000000">--------------------------------</font><br/><br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">1. Underweight:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">If your BMI is less than 18.5, focus on gaining weight through a balanced diet rich in nutrients. Consult with a nutritionist for a personalized plan.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">2. Normal Weight:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Congratulations! Maintain your weight through a healthy diet, regular exercise, and good sleep. Monitor your BMI regularly for any changes.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">3. Overweight:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Work on losing weight gradually through a combination of a calorie-controlled diet and increased physical activity. Consult a healthcare professional for guidance.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">4. Obesity:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Obesity poses health risks. Seek professional help for a comprehensive weight management plan, including diet, exercise, and possibly medical intervention.</font><br/><br/>
          <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/>
          <b><font color="#004281">Healthy Living Across Ages:</font></b><br/>
          <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/><br/>
          <br/>

        <font color="#000000">Leading a healthy life involves different strategies at various ages. Here are some age-specific recommendations:</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">1. Childhood (0-12 years):</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Encourage a balanced diet, active play, and sufficient sleep. Limit screen time and foster healthy habits early.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">2. Adolescence (13-19 years):</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Emphasize balanced nutrition, regular exercise, and proper hydration. Educate about the importance of mental health and self-care.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">3. Adulthood (20-60 years):</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Maintain a healthy weight, exercise regularly, and prioritize stress management. Regular health check-ups are essential for preventive care.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">4. Senior Years (60+ years):</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Focus on a nutrient-rich diet, engage in low-impact exercises, and stay socially connected. Regular health screenings become even more crucial.</font><br/><br/><br/>
          <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/><br/> <font color="#004281">20 Tips for a Healthier Life:</font></b><br/> <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/><br/>
        <b><br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">1.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Stay hydrated by drinking plenty of water.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">2.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Include a variety of fruits and vegetables in your diet.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">3.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Engage in regular physical activity to maintain a healthy lifestyle.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">4.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Get enough quality sleep each night to support overall well-being.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">5.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Limit the intake of sugary and processed foods in your diet.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">6.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Practice stress-reducing activities, such as meditation or deep breathing.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">7.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Maintain a healthy weight through a balanced diet and regular exercise.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">8.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Avoid smoking and limit alcohol consumption for better health.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">9.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Prioritize mental health by seeking support and practicing self-care.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">10.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Stay socially connected with friends and family for emotional well-being.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">11.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Practice good hygiene habits to prevent the spread of illnesses.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">12.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Limit screen time and take breaks to protect your eyes and posture.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">13.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Challenge your mind with activities like puzzles or learning new skills.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">14.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Foster positive relationships and surround yourself with supportive individuals.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">15.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Practice gratitude to promote a positive outlook on life.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">16.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Limit exposure to environmental pollutants for better respiratory health.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">17.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Educate yourself about your own health and make informed decisions.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">18.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Schedule regular health check-ups and screenings for early detection of issues.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">19.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Set realistic goals and celebrate your achievements along the way.</font><br/> <br/>
<b><font color="#004281">20.</font></b> <font color="#000000">Find joy in hobbies and activities that bring fulfillment to your life.</font><br/> <br/>
        <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/><b><font color="#004281">10 TIPS To Be Safe..</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#004281">________________________</font><br/><br/>

        <b><font color="#004281">1. Measure and Watch Your Weight:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Keeping track of your body weight on a daily or weekly basis will help you see what you’re losing and/or what
        you’re gaining.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">2. Limit Unhealthy Foods and Eat Healthy Meals:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Do not forget to eat breakfast and choose a nutritious meal with more protein and fiber and less fat, sugar, and
        calories. For more information on weight-control foods and dietary recommendations, please check the following
        website: <a href="http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/obesity-prevention-source/obesity-causes/diet-and-weight/">www.hsph.harvard.edu/obesity-prevention-source/obesity-causes/diet-and-weight/</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">3. Take Multivitamin Supplements:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">To make sure you have sufficient levels of nutrients, taking a daily multivitamin supplement is a good idea,
        especially when you do not have a variety of vegetables and fruits at home. Many micronutrients are vital to your
        immune system, including vitamins A, B6, B12, C, D, and E, as well as zinc, iron, copper, selenium, and magnesium.
        However, there’s currently NO available evidence that adding any supplements or “miracle mineral supplements”
        to your diet will help protect you from the virus or increase recovery. In some cases, high doses of vitamins can be
        bad for your health.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">4. Drink Water and Stay Hydrated, and Limit Sugared Beverages:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Drink water regularly to stay healthy, but there is NO evidence that drinking water frequently (e.g. every 15
        minutes) can help prevent any viral infection. For more information on drinking water and coronavirus, please
        check the following EPA website: <a href="http://www.epa.gov/coronavirus/coronavirus-and-drinking-water-and-wastewater/">www.epa.gov/coronavirus/coronavirus-and-drinking-water-and-wastewater</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">5. Exercise Regularly and Be Physically Active:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">At this time, at-home workouts may be a good idea. But you can also walk your dog or run outside. Be sure you
        know what’s going on in your area and if there are any restrictions or mandatory self-quarantines. For more
        information on how to stay physically active while at home, please check the ACSM website: <a href="http://www.acsm.org/read-research/newsroom/news-releases/news-detail/2020/03/16/staying-physically-active-during-covid-19-pandemic/">www.acsm.org/read-research/newsroom/news-releases/news-detail/2020/03/16/staying-physically-active-during-covid-19-pandemic</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">6. Reduce Sitting and Screen Time:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Exercise can’t immunize you from your sedentary time. Even people who exercise regularly could be at increased
        risk for diabetes and heart disease and stroke if they spend lots of time sitting behind computers. Practically
        speaking, you could consider taking breaks from sedentary time, such as walking around the office/room a couple
        of times in a day.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">7. Get Enough Good Sleep:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">There is a very strong connection between sleep quality and quantity and your immune system. You can keep your
        immune system functioning properly by getting seven to eight hours of sleep each night. For more information,
        please check the CDC website: <a href="http://www.cdc.gov/sleep/index.html">www.cdc.gov/sleep/index.html</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">8. Go Easy on Alcohol and Stay Sober:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">Drinking alcohol does not protect you from the coronavirus infection. Don’t forget that those alcohol calories can
        add up quickly. Alcohol should always be consumed in moderation. Please see the recommendations by the AHA:
        <a href="http://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/nutrition-basics/alcohol-and-heart-health/">www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/nutrition-basics/alcohol-and-heart-health</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">9. Find Ways to Manage Your Emotions:</font></b><br/><br/>
        <font color="#000000">It is common for people to have feelings of fear, anxiety, sadness, and uncertainty during a pandemic. To minimize
        stress-related weight gain, you use this information about stress and coping provided by the CDC: <a href="http://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prepare/managing-stress-anxiety.html">www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/prepare/managing-stress-anxiety.html</a>.</font><br/>
        <br/>
        <b><font color="#004281">10. Use an App to Keep Track of Your Movement, Sleep, and Heart Rate:</font></b><br/>
        <font color="#000000">A reminder: People with serious chronic medical conditions, including extreme obesity, diabetes, and heart disease
        are at a higher risk of experiencing complications and getting very sick from the COVID-19 infection. They should talk
        to their medical providers and listen to their advice.</font>
    ]]>
</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="have_not_account">Have Not Account?</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register Here</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="medicine_name">Medicine Name</string>
    <string name="add_medicine">Add Medicine</string>
</resources>

